<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>SHEN Jiamin's Home</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on SHEN Jiamin's Home</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><copyright>&amp;copy; 2022 SHEN Jiamin</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Setup Printers from NUS SoC on Ubuntu</title><link>/posts/2022-06-21/soc-printer/</link><pubDate>Tue, 21 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2022-06-21/soc-printer/</guid><description>Install a Printer Driver Visit Lexmark Website and search for the driver for the printer you want to use. You may find the device model from dochub. Download the corresponding deb package and install it using
$ sudo apt install ./Lexmark-UPD-PPD-Files-[some-version-number].amd64.deb Setup the Printer Launch the config by executing
$ sudo system-config-printer Select Device Click &amp;ldquo;Add&amp;rdquo; and choose &amp;ldquo;Network Printer&amp;rdquo; &amp;gt; &amp;ldquo;Windows Printer via SAMBA&amp;rdquo; from the &amp;ldquo;Devices&amp;rdquo; frame. Enter nusstu/ntsxx.comp.nus.edu.sg/psxddd after &amp;ldquo;smb://&amp;rdquo; Use a domain that&amp;rsquo;s appropriate for you.</description></item><item><title>Use HTTPS? Login to Github Using gh</title><link>/posts/2022-06-19/github-https/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2022-06-19/github-https/</guid><description>Managing Personal Access Token from GitHub manually, to access to repositories via HTTPS, can be tedious. This blog talks about authentication using GitHub cli, which comes with a auth module. It can help to keep the token for HTTPS use.
Installation Install gh following their official README. You&amp;rsquo;ll need git, of course. Authentication Execute the command below to login to your GitHub account and then following the interactive procedure.
gh auth login --scopes repo For the first two questions:</description></item><item><title>Try OpenNIC on U250</title><link>/posts/2022-06-10/open-nic-u250/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/2022-06-10/open-nic-u250/</guid><description>Overview The AMD OpenNIC Project consists of a hardware design (OpenNIC shell) and two software drivers (OpenNIC driver and OpenNIC DPDK).
This article is base on open-nic-shell at commit 542a487 and open-nic-driver at commit 2fa9668.
Tips on the Hardware Part It&amp;rsquo;s easy to get an FPGA bitstream by following the README.
There are two QSFP28 interfaces on the Alveo U250 Data Center Accelerator Card. But the shell enables only one of them by default. Thus, if both of them are needed, do set the parameter -num_cmac_port to 2.</description></item></channel></rss>